Contact

zaide77alternative@gmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/zaide-mangondato-78758a128 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Web Development
Microsoft PowerPoint
Visual C#

Zaide Mangondato

Businessman | Web Developer | Software Developer Region X - Northern Mindanao, Philippines

Summary

TRAINING/SEMINAR/WORKSHOP ATTENDED

Machine Learning and Virtual Reality, DEVCON Capitol University, Cagayan de Oro City Oct. 1, 2016

Winning Discipline Seminar Capitol University, Cagayan de Oro City Aug. 27, 2016

Hybrid Mobile Application Development Tutorial and Workshop Capitol University, Cagayan de Oro City Aug. 20, 2016

Joint Leadership Training Seminar Capitol University, Cagayan de Oro City Jul. 30, 2016

CS Research Congress
Capitol University, Cagayan de Oro City
April 6, 2016

Doing PHP the Right Way – Software Freedom Day 2015 Capitol University, Cagayan de Oro City Sept. 19, 2015

Virtual Reality – Software Freedom Day 2015 Capitol University, Cagayan de Oro City Sept. 19, 2015

Cisco Skills
Capitol University, Cagayan de Oro City
Oct. 9, 2013

Experience

Self-employed Developer March 2017 - Present Kalilangan, Bukidnon

Kalilangan Integrated Transport Terminal Terminal Operator January 2018 - April 2019 (1 year 4 months) West Poblacion, Kalilangan Bukidnon

Education

Capitol University

Degree, Information Technology · (2012 - 2017)